jacquielawson.com 2007-12-23

# Jacquie Lawson privacy policy, cookies, history & data information collected

| 

### Name and address data

When you join jacquielawson.com you are invited to provide us with your e-mail address, name, address, telephone number, country of origin, and credit card information (if you choose to pay by credit card). All this information is optional except your e-mail address (which we use to identify you when you log on), your country (which we have to know in order to determine whether to account for Value Added Tax on your membership fee), and, if you choose to pay via credit, your credit card information.

We will not divulge any of this information to any third party now or at any time in the future without first asking for your permission.

### Emails we may send you

The following are some of the circumstances in which we will send you e-mails.

  * **Newsletters.** We will send you emails detailing new e-card releases and new features of our website.  
 
  * **Card Notifications.** When you order any e-cards from our site, we will email you to tell you when the cards have been sent, and also when they are picked up by the recipients. If a card cannot be delivered we will also send you the non-delivery notice.  
 
  * **Birthday Reminders.** If you enter the birthdates of your friends and family in your jacquielawson.com address book, then we will send you an email to remind you about each birthday.  
 
  * **Renewal reminders.** When your membership is about to expire, we will send you renewal reminders. If you have selected auto-renew, we will automatically renew your membership.  
 
  * **Administrative and help emails.** In addition, we will of course reply to your help requests, and we may send you miscellaneous administrative correspondence - password reminders, confirmation of payment, renewal confirmations, and so on. 

From time to time, we may also send you important updates about our products and services. You can always opt not to receive non-Administrative emails by using the My Details page of our website (you have to log on first) or using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of emails. Please allow five to seven days for processing. You can also cancel your membership at any time.

### Cookies

When you log on, our server looks up your membership number on our database and sends it to your computer in the form of a "cookie". This cookie is used by our software simply for the purpose of detecting that you have logged on and are authorised to send cards and visit any member-only parts of the site. The cookie is a "session" (as opposed to "permanent") cookie, and when you exit your browser session this cookie is automatically deleted (which is why you have to log on again every time you revisit the site).

If you check the "remember me" box, our server sends your computer a cookie, so that you will not have to log on. The cookie will log you on automatically every time you come to the site.

### Auto-Renew

We will store your payment information in our database so that we may renew your membership. We will not automatically renew your membership unless you choose the auto-renew option.

### Card History

As a necessary part of the process of sending e-cards, the recipient details and personal messages that you enter when you send a card are stored in our database. This also enables you to review cards you have sent by using our Card History page.

We will not divulge these details to any third party.

### Analysis of Data

We may use the information collected on the site (principally membership information, history of cards sent, and information submitted by you using our feedback form) to improve our service. For example, if we find that many people are sending a particular type of card, we may decide to develop more cards of that type. Any personally identifiable information gained in this way will not be shared with any third party.

### Storage of Data

We store the information collected on the site (principally membership information, history of cards sent, and information submitted by you using our feedback form) in the United States. By being a Member of the site, you agree to have your information stored in the United States. We assure you that the storage and processing of your information will be in compliance with applicable international laws.

### Changes to Policy

By becoming a Member, you agree to the terms of this privacy policy. We may change the terms of this privacy policy by updating this page. You should periodically visit the Site to determine the Terms to which you are bound. If any of the rules contained in the privacy policy or any future changes to the privacy policy are not acceptable to you, you should cancel your licence. Your continued use of the Site now, or following the posting of any changes to this privacy policy, will indicate acceptance by you of such changes.

close window

|
